Guide to The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings AIA.089
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings
1976-2001
1999-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Flannelly, Adrian
Irish Radio Network USA
AIA.089
6.08 linear feet in 4 flat boxes and 2 record cartons
327 audiocassettes
Adrian Flannelly (born 1942) is an Irish broadcaster and the Chairman and CEO of Irish Radio Network USA. He hosts The Adrian Flannelly Show, a weekly radio program he began in 1969, which consists of a combination of music, international and national news, cultural news, economic analysis and commentary, as well as interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. Flannelly has used his radio show to highlight social and political issues concerning Irish and Irish American communities, including United States immigration reform and visa lotteries. This collection consists of 256 audiocassette recordings of his weekly Irish American talk radio program The Adrian Flannelly Show, dated approximately 1978-2000. The collection also contains an additional 71 audiocassettes, dated approximately 1976-2001, whose affiliation to the show is unclear.
Scope and Contents
The Adrian Flannelly Show Recordings consists of 327 audiocassette recordings donated by Adrian Flannelly. The materials in the collection date from 1976 to 2001 with the bulk of materials dating 1999-2000. Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show contains 256 audiocassette recordings of Flannelly's weekly Irish American talk radio program, dated approximately 1978-2000. Flannelly's show consists of a combination of music, international and national news, cultural news, economic analysis and commentary, as well as interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. Topics like immigration reform and conflict in Northern Ireland are discussed frequently. Series II: Additional Tapes contains 71 audiocassette recordings, dated approximately 1976-2001, whose association with Flannelly's radio program is unclear.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into two series:
Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show
Series II: Additional Tapes
Within each series, the audiocassettes have been arranged in chronological order. Undated material was arranged in alphabetical order when possible.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Adrian Flannelly in March 2020; the accession number associated with this gift is 2020.020.
Biographical Note
Adrian Flannelly (born 1942) is an Irish broadcaster and the Chairman and CEO of Irish Radio Network USA. He hosts The Adrian Flannelly Show, a weekly radio program he began in 1969, which consists of a combination of music, international and national news, cultural news, economic analysis and commentary, as well as interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. Flannelly has used his radio show to highlight social and political issues concerning Irish and Irish American communities, including United States immigration reform and visa lotteries. He also serves as the Irish Cultural Liason for the Irish Hunger Memorial in Battery Park City, has received numerous honors from Irish and Irish American organizations in the greater New York City area, and in 2016 was awarded an honorary Doctorate degree from Quinnipiac University.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Appraisal
In 2021, 7 duplicate tapes were deaccessioned from the collection.
Radio programs.; Irish Americans -- Ethnic identity.; Irish Americans -- History.; Irish Americans -- New York (N.Y.); Irish Americans -- New York (State) -- New York -- Political activity.; Irish Americans -- Social life and customs.; Northern Ireland -- History -- 1968-1998; Peace movements -- Northern Ireland; Emigration and immigration law -- United States.; Radio broadcasters; Flannelly, Adrian
- The Adrian Flannelly Show, 1978-2000; 256 audiocassettes in 4 flatboxes and 2 record cartons
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains 256 audiocassette recordings of Flannelly's radio program.
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1978 September (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0001)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1978 September 23-24 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0002)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1978 December 1 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0003)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1983 April 30, 1983 1 May (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0004)
  - Flannelly, 1983 June 4 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0005)
  - A. Flannelly Show, 1983 September 24 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0006)
  - A. Flannelly Show, 1983 October 8 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0007)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1983 October 29 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0008)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1983 November 11 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0009)
  - A. Flannelly Show, 1983 November 12 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0010)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1983 December 3 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0011)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1983 December 10 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0012)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1984 January 21 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0013)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1984 January 30 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0014)
  - A. Flannelly, 1984 December 31 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0015)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 January 5 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0016)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 January 19 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0017)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 January 20 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0018)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 January 26 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0019)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 2 February 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0328)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 February 9 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0020)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 February 23 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0021)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 February 24 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0022)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 March 2 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0023)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 March 9 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0024)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 March 10 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0025)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 March 16 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0026)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 March 23 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0027)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 March 24 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0028)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 March 30 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0029)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 April 6 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0030)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show - No Guests, 1985 April 20 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0031)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 April 27 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0032)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 May 5 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0033)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 May 11 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0034)
  - A. Flannelly Show, 1985 May 17 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0035)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 May 18 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0036)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 June 1 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0037)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 June 2 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0038)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 June 8 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0039)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show (Gov Cuomo), 1985 June 15 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0040)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 June 16 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0041)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 June 22 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0042)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 June 29 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0043)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 August 3 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0044)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 August 25 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0045)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #2, 1985 September 1 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0046)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #4, 1985 September 1 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0047)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #1, 1985 September 8 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0048)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #3, 1985 September 8 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0049)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 September 21 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0050)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 September 22 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0051)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 October 3 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0052)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1985 October 6 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0053)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 October 19 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0054)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1985 October 20 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0055)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 November 2 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0057)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 November 9 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0056)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 November 16 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0058)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 December 8 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0059)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 December 15 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0060)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1985 December 22 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0061)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 January 11 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0062)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 January 19 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0063)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 January 25 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0064)
  - Flannelly Show, 1986 February 8 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0065)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 February 15 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0066)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 February 22 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0067)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 March (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0068)
  - Aircheck - Flannelly Show, 1986 March 1 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0069)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 March 16 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0070)
  - A. Flannelly, 1986 March 29 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0071)
  - A. Flannelly Show Pt. 3, 1986 April 5 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0072)
  - Flannelly Aircheck (11:30 pm - 12 Noon), 1986 April 5 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0073)
  - Flannelly Aircheck (12 Noon - 1 pm), 1986 April 5 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0074)
  - A. Flannelly Show, 1986 April 12 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0075)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1986 May 3 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0076)
  - A. Flannelly Show, 1986 May 10 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0077)
  - A. Flannelly Show, 1986 June 28 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0078)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1987 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0079)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1987 January (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0080)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1987 January 30 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0081)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1988 January 25 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0082)
  - A. Flannelly/Monsignor J. Murray, 1988 February 13 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0083)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1999 January 2 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0084)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1999 January 9 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0085)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1999 January 10 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0086)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1999 January 16 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0087)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1999 January 17 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0088)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1999 January 23 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0089)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1999 January 24 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0090)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, 1999 January 30 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0091)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, 1999 January 31 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0092)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, 1999 February 6 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0093)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1999 February 7 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0094)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, 1999 February 13 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0095)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, 1999 February 14 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0096)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1999 February 20 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0097)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1999 February 21 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0098)
  - Adrian Flannelly, 1999 February 27 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0099)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, 1999 February 28 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0100)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, 1999 March 6 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0101)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, 1999 March 7 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0102)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, 1999 March 13 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0103)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1999 March 14 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0104)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1999 March 20 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0105)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, 1999 March 21 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0106)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Sat Show, 1999 March 27 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0107)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, 1999 April 3 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0108)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, 1999 April 4 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0109)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 April 10 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0110)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 April 11 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0111)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 April 17 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0112)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 April 18 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0113)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 April 24 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0114)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 April 25 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0115)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 1 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0116)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 2 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0117)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 8 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0118)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 9 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0119)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 15 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0120)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 16 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0121)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 22 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0122)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 23 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0123)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 29 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0124)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 May 30 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0125)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 5 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0126)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 6 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0127)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 12 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0128)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 13 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0129)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 19 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0130)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 20 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0131)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 26 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0132)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 June 27 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0133)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 3 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0134)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 4 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0135)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 10 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0136)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 11 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0137)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 17 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0138)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 18 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0139)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 24 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0140)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 July 25 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0141)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 July 31 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0142)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 1999 August 1 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0143)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 August 7 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0144)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 August 8 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0145)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 August 14 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0146)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 August 15 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0147)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 August 22 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0148)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 August 28 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0149)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 September 4 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0150)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 September 5 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0151)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 September 11 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0152)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 September 12 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0153)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 September 18 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0154)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 September 19 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0155)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 September 25 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0156)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 September 26 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0157)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 October 2 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0158)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 October 3 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0159)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 October 9 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0160)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 October 10 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0161)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 October 16 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0162)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 October 17 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0163)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 October 23 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0164)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 October 24 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0165)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 October 30 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0166)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 November 6 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0167)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 November 7 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0168)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 November 13 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0169)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 November14 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0170)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 November 20 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0171)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 November 21 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0172)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 November 27 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0173)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 December 4 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0174)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 December 5 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0175)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 December 11 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0176)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 1999 December 12 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0177)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 December 18 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0178)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (1st Hour), 1999 December 25 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0179)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (2nd Hour), 1999 December 25 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0180)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (Hour 1), 1999 December 26 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0181)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (Hour 2), 1999 December 26 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0182)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, 1999 December 28 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0183)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 January 1 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0184)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 January 2 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0185)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 2000 January 8 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0186)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 2000 January 15 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0187)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 2000 January 16 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0188)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 January 23 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0189)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 January 29 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0190)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 February 5 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0191)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 February 6 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0192)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 February 12 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0193)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 February 13 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0194)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 February 19 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0195)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 February 26 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0196)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 February 27 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0197)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 March 4 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0198)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 March 5 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0199)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 March 11 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0200)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 March 12 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0201)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 March 19 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0202)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 March 26 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0203)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 April 1 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0204)
  - Irish Radio, 2000 April 2 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0205)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, 2000 April 8 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0206)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 April 9 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0207)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 April 15 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0208)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 April 16 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0209)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 April 22 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0210)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 April 23 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0211)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 April 29 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0212)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 April 30 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0213)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 6 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0214)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 7 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0215)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 13 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0216)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 14 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0217)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 20 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0218)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 21 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0219)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 27 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0220)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 May 28 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0221)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 June 3 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0222)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 June 10 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0223)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 June 17 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0224)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 June 18 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0225)
  - Adrian Flannelly Radio Shows, 2000 June 24 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0226)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 June 25 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0227)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 July 1 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0228)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 July 8 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0229)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 July 15 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0230)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 July 22 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0231)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 July 29 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0232)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 August 5 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0233)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 August 12 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0234)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 August 19 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0235)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 August 26 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0236)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 September 2 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0237)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 September 9 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0238)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 September 16 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0239)